wednesdaygift.com 2014-05-20

# WednesdayGift - Every Wednesday A New Gift

We want our users and customers to always be aware of any information we collect, how we use it, and under what cicumstances, if any, we disclose it. We are also committed to providing you with the very best experience we can on our Website. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our Web site. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically.

We respect each site visitors right to personal privacy. We collect and use information throuhout our website only as disclosed in this Privacy Policy. This statement applies solely to information collected on this website.

We collect and use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site, and to help identify you. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information, and for other purposes.

We use some outside ad companies to display ads on the site. These ads may contain cookies. While we do not use cookies in our website, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information.

We have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Our servers have strict security in place to prevent an intruder from retrieving personal information about our users. Staff overlook server access daily to ensure the above holds true.

Our site contains links to other sites and file downloads from other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

We work with some third party that serves ads to the site. To find out more about how they manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to their sites : Affili.net, Advertising.com, Burst Media, Google Inc, Fastclick and Clickbank.com

We do not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or companies ever. At no time do we see personal credit card information on purchases. We never sell or rent email addresses from people who have joined our mailing list. Your confidentiality and trust is of paramount importance to us.

We require information from the user on our order form. A user must provide contact information (such as name, eMail and shipping address) and possible financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). If we have trouble processing an order, we use the information to contact the user.

By using our Website, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information by us as outlined in this Privacy Policy.

Be Sociable, Share!

  *
